I am sleep-deprived I've been
sleep-deprived ever since I had kids I'm
not blaming them I'm just saying things
changed and it's not just the kids my
wife has that that deal were restless
leg syndrome you know I'm talking about
all right
so there's nothing less relaxing than to
be startled in the middle of the night
and look at the covers next to you I
[Music]
thought I'm gonna pull back the coverage
he's gonna have cloven hooves this is
this is not I remember I took those vows
seriously you know for richer or for
poorer in sickness and in health nowhere
do I remember you have to stick with her
if she's got the Crazy Legs the only
time I get any good sleep anymore is
when I go in for some sort of surgery
yeah most people dread that you know I'm
up to like one colonoscopy a month I
gotta say uh take daddy to the happy
place I know
I'm gonna get a couple of good hours of
shut-eye there so so my wife and I now
this year makes 23 years of marriage and
I have nothing bad to say about marriage
it's actually you know there's you know
we I don't tell everybody this by the
way but we only knew each other for
three months before we got married
because well you know what
everybody's got a checklist in your head
even if you don't admit it and we were
checking everything off so it was like
why wait everything we we saw eye to eye
on you know we both don't like deep
fancy we hate to dance she has a slight
appreciation for the Three Stooges
neither of us can read and she's
allergic to gold so you can build a
whole build a whole life on that and I
mean we don't see eye to eye on
everything she loves to shop that's
probably my least favorite thing to do
I don't like to shop but you start to
support your spouse you know they do
things that with you that they probably
have no interest in doing I'll go
shopping with her but I have to find
something to keep myself entertained you
know because that one of my favorite
things to do is I like to hide one of
those racks of clothes and then when
somebody comes by which eventually they
will they they pull the clothes back I'm
always there to hand them a garment of
clothing doing my best Jack Nicholson
here's your Spanx
so this last anniversary uh my wife
broke it to me that uh and she did a
nice way but she says you know you
always give me stuff that's real
practical for the anniversary why don't
you maybe get something a little more
intimate and kind of hurt my feelings a
little bit because I care about what she
cares about I listen to her very
carefully I remember one year seems like
non-stop she'd say you know I really
like to paint and so that anniversary I
got a real nice a 12 foot ladder and she
was talking about but so I I capitalized
on that word drove beat on that word
intimate and I I ended up at a
Victoria's Secret I've never been in one
of those stores in my life I didn't open
my eyes all time I was in there I just
grabbed something at random off the
shelf got at home it was one of those
slinky bras which you probably seen a
slinky hanging from each cover which is
real handy when it gets dirty she rolls
down the stairs goes in the washer all
by itself that's probably the best thing
I've ever stolen you know
[Music]
but so much better being married than
being single I never had like I had a
lot of blind dates friends always wanted
to fix me up I don't think one of them
materialized to a second date even when
I thought it was gonna be you know maybe
something was gonna work out I remember
this one time ice pick stuff this this
girl she was attractive and she said
something just threw me off I guess we
were at a nice restaurant to Long John
Silver's and she said she goes will you
please excuse me I've got to pee like a
racehorse what do you say to that oh I
hear that I've got a poop like a
Clydesdale this is a dream date right
here nearly choked on my hush puppies I
oh hey did you know that drive our
comedy has their own app you can
download it right now and see my whole
special